watchprosite.com 2019-07-02

# Watchprosite - Official WatchProSite Reviews of luxury Wristwatches for Collectors & buyers

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Pubzap LLC and Puristspro LLC (herinafter HOST) we have a few fundamental principles: 

  * We don't ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can't stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * In our blogging products, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what's visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our support team. 

Pubzap LLC & Puristspro LLC. ("HOST") operates several websites including www.HOST.com, www.watchprosite.com and www.puristspro.com. It is HOST's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. 

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, HOST collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. HOST's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how HOST's visitors use its website. From time to time, HOST may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

HOST also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on WordPress.com blogs. HOST only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left. 

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to HOST's websites choose to interact with HOST in ways that require HOST to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that HOST gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at watchprosite.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with HOST - by purchasing access to a service, for example - are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, HOST collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with HOST. HOST does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

## Aggregated Statistics

HOST may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. HOST uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your computers hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information. You can read Google's privacy policy here for further information [ http://www.google.com/privacy.html ].

For instance, HOST may monitor the most popular posts on the watchprosite.com site. HOST may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, HOST does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

HOST discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on HOST's behalf or to provide services available at HOST's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using HOST's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. HOST will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, HOST discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when HOST believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of HOST, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an HOST website and have supplied your email address, HOST may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with HOST and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. HOST takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. HOST uses cookies to help HOST identify and track visitors, their usage of HOST website, and their website access preferences. HOST visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using HOST's websites, with the drawback that certain features of HOST's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

## Business Transfers

If HOST, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that HOST goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of HOST may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

## Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by HOST and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

## Social Media Platforms

Communication, engagement and actions taken through external social media platforms that this website and its owners participate on are custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively. Users are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate / engage upon them with due care and caution in regard to their own privacy and personal details. This website nor its owners will ever ask for personal or sensitive information through social media platforms and encourage users wishing to discuss sensitive details to contact them through primary communication channels such as by telephone or email.

This website may use social sharing buttons which help share web content directly from web pages to the social media platform in question. Users are advised before using such social sharing buttons that they do so at their own discretion and note that the social media platform may track and save your request to share a web page respectively through your social media platform account. 

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, HOST may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in HOST's sole discretion. HOST encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
